# LAUREN MILES

#### FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Detroit, MI 937-329-1424 laurenmiles.dev@gmail.com

## **ABOUT ME**

Software Developer with experience creating modern websites, applications, and automations. Works well in collaborative settings to accomplish common goals, bringing creative ideas and solutions to the table. Has a keen eye to detail to ensure work is completed to a high standard. Has experience working on front-end and back-end development.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

TECH ELEVATOR, COLUMBUS, OH (REMOTE)

FEB 2022 - MAY 2023

- Contributed to the Platforms and Infrastructure team by maintaining and improving the BootcampOS application by adding new features
- Architected and developed workflows (using Azure Functions) to automate internal processes resulting in reduced workload for departments and more time for other responsibilities
- Collaborated with team to support all company applications by addressing support and feature requests reported by employees and students

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

NATIONWIDE CHILDREN'S HOSPITAL, COLUMBUS, OH (REMOTE)

OCT 2021 - FEB 2022

- Supported the Marketing team by making updates to the main website framework using Sitecore
- Improved main website by ensuring pages and forms met accessibility requirements
- Maintained existing applications by addressing bugs and support requests reported in the ticketing system

#### ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE DEVELOPER/CONSULTANT

KIZAN TECHNOLOGIES, LOUISVILLE, KY (REMOTE)

JUN 2020 - OCT 2021

- Contributed to the Custom Application Development team by creating custom applications for clients using Microsoft technologies
- Worked directly with clients to address any feature or support requests
- Exceeded career goals by being utilized as a full time developer within 2 months of employment

#### **EDUCATION**

## ○ CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION | APR 2020

TECH ELEVATOR, COLUMBUS, OH

Attended a 14 week .NET coding bootcamp learning how to create web-based software using C#.

#### **TECH SKILLS**

- C#
- .NET
- TypeScript
- JavaScript
- Node.js
- Next.js
- React
- · Ruby on Rails
- Microsoft Azure
- SQL

## CERTIFICATIONS

## MICROSOFT AZUREFUNDAMENTALS (AZ-900)

APR 2020

Demonstrated foundational level knowledge of cloud services and how those services are provided with Microsoft Azure.

## **PROJECTS**

- KSBA Portal
- BootcampOS
- Nationwide Children's Hospital website
- Women Wine & Web Design

To learn about the details of these projects, please visit the link to my website below. Under the Projects tab, there is a comprehensive list of the major projects I've worked on and the technologies used.

#### LINKS

#### LINKEDIN

/laurenmmiles

#### **GITHUB**

/laurenmilesdev

#### **WEBSITE**

portfolio.laurenmilesdev.com